https://www.montereymushrooms.com/privacy-policy

Effective Date: May 28, 2019
Thank you for visiting www.montereymushrooms.com (“website”), which is owned by Monterey Mushrooms, Inc. (“Monterey Mushrooms,” “we,” “us,” or “our”).
Table of Contents
Scope of This Policy
Your Consent
This Policy is Part of Our Terms of Use
Privacy Notices
Your Consent to Other Agreements
Types of Personal Information We Collect
Information About Third-Party Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising
How We Use Personal Information Collected Through The Services
Links to Other Websites
User Generated Content
Use of Aggregated Information
Use of Survey Information
Your Choices
How to Access, Update or Correct Your Personal Information
Steps We Take to Safeguard your Personal Information
How We Share Your Personal Information With Others
Children Under the Age of Thirteen
This Policy May Change
Definitions
Contact Us
Scope of This Policy
This privacy policy (this “Policy”) applies to information collected on the website or on other websites that are owned or controlled by Monterey Mushrooms and on which we post a link to this Policy, and it applies to information collected when you place an order with us (“order”) (collectively, the website and orders are referred to as the “Services”).
Some of the information we collect through the Services may be “Personal Information” - information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us. Other information may be nonpersonally identifiable, such as information collected by cookies.
Your Consent
Please take a few minutes to read and understand our Privacy Policy so that you know how we collect, use, and share your Personal Information. By using the Services, you are consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by this Policy, you may not access or use the Services.
This Policy is Part of Our Terms of Use
This Policy is part of the Terms of Use that govern your use of the Services. A link to our Terms of Use is provided at the bottom of each page of the Services and our App. Any capitalized terms used herein that are not defined have the same definitions as in the Terms of Use.
Privacy Notices
This Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by “privacy notices” posted on the Services. These privacy notices provide a level of detail that we cannot provide in this more general description of our privacy practices. For example, certain pages of the Services may contain privacy notices providing details about the Personal Information we collect on those pages, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the ways we use that information. Privacy practices related to specific contests we offer will appear in the contest rules.
Your Consent to Other Agreements
When you sign up to use a special feature of the Services, you may be asked to agree to special terms governing your use of the special feature (“Additional Terms”). In such cases, you may be asked to expressly consent to the special terms, for example, by checking a box or clicking on a button marked “I agree.” If any of the terms of the Additional Terms are different than the terms of this Policy, the terms of the Additional Terms will supplement or amend this Policy, but only with respect to the matters governed by the Additional Terms.
Types of Personal Information We Collect
Information You Manually Provide. Monterey Mushrooms collects the Personal Information you manually provide (using your keyboard, mouse, or touchpad) when you use the Services. For example, we collect the information you provide when you create an account, place an order, ask us a question, or otherwise interact with the Services. Some of the information you manually provide may be Personal Information. For example, if you create an account on our website, we may ask you to provide your name, email address, and other information. If you place an order, we may ask for your credit card information. Some features and services require additional Personal Information or demographic information. For example, when you enter contests and/or sweepstakes you may be asked to provide your phone number and/or email address so that we can reach you in the event you win a prize. We may also collect any Personal Information you submit on or through the Services when you provide feedback or contact us with questions. Some of the information you post to the Services may constitute User Generated Content. All User Generated Content must comply with our Terms of Use.
Information Others Manually Provide. In some areas of the Services, users can submit information about other people. For example, if someone orders a gift or gift card or certificate online and wants to send it directly to you, they must submit your name and address. We use this information to send the gift to you. We also store this information so that the user does not have to reenter it the next time he/she wants to send a gift to you.
Information From Third-Party Social Media Platforms. You may be able to choose to register, log-on, or enhance your profile on the Services through a third-party social media platform, such as Facebook Connect. By doing this, you are asking the third-party social media platform to send us registration information from your profile on that platform. If you choose to share content or to otherwise post information through the Services to a third-party service, or vice versa, that information may be publicly displayed. Similarly, if you post information on a third-party service that references us (for example, by using a hashtag associated with us in your post), your post may be published on the Services or otherwise in accordance with the terms of that third party. Also, both we and the third-party may have access to certain information about you and your use of the Services and the third-party service. We treat that information as we do any other information you give to us when you register, log-on, or enhance your profile. After you have connected, the third-party may also send us additional information from your profile that allows us to offer certain functionalities on the pages you view. The information collected and stored by the third-party remains subject to the third party’s privacy practices, including whether the third-party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party service.
Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser. We collect information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser. This information typically includes your IP address, the identity of your Internet service provider, the name and version of your operating system, the name and version of your browser, the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. Generally, we do not link the information provided by your browser to your Personal Information.
More About IP Addresses. Your IP address is the identifier assigned to your particular computer when you access the Internet. Depending on how you connect to the Internet, your IP address may always be the same, or it may change each time you access the Internet. IP addresses do not include your name, email address or other Personal Information, but in some cases, they can be used to identify you. For example, if you have registered with the Services, we may link your IP address to account information that identifies you personally. We may also provide your IP address to our third-party service providers who can use it to identify information such as your state and zip code. If we suspect inappropriate or criminal activity or a threat to the Services or their users, we may also share our server logs—which contain users’ IP addresses—with the appropriate investigative authorities, who could use that information to trace and identify individuals.
Cookies and Similar Technologies. Most websites use cookies and/or similar technologies to place information about a user’s visit to that website in a small data text file that is stored on the user’s computer. In general, we use cookies and other web technologies to:
collect information about the ways visitors use the Services—which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page;
support the features and functionality of the Services—for example, to save you the trouble of reentering information already in our database or to prompt the settings you established on previous visits; and
personalize your experience when you use the Services, including by serving targeted advertisements.
Generally, the information we collect using these web technologies does not identify you personally. If, however, you have created a user account, we may link the information we collect using these web technologies to other information that identifies you personally.
If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may be able to set the browser of your computer or mobile or tablet device to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is delivered. You may also be able to delete our cookies as soon as you leave the Services. Although you are not required to accept our cookies when you visit the Services, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features and functionality of the Services.
Information from your mobile or tablet device. If you access our website through your mobile or tablet device, we may automatically collect certain information from or about your mobile or tablet device. The types of information we may collect include the type of device you use, your device’s unique ID, the IP address of your device, your device’s operating system and the type of mobile or tablet Internet browsers you use.
Information About Third-Party Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising
In addition to the cookies Monterey Mushrooms delivers to your computer or mobile or tablet device through the Services, certain third parties may deliver cookies to you for a variety of reasons. For example, we may use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with the Services. To learn more about Google Analytics, click here.
Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer or mobile or tablet device for the purpose of tracking your online behaviors across nonaffiliated websites and delivering targeted advertisements either on the Services or on other websites. You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on the Services. For example, if you don’t want information about your visit to the Services sent to Google Analytics, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking here. Please note that the Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to Monterey Mushrooms.
In addition, if you would like to opt-out of having interest-based information collected by certain entities during your visits to the Services or other websites, please click here. You will be directed to an industry-developed website that contains mechanisms for choosing whether each listed entity may collect and use data for online behavioral advertising purposes. It may be that some of the third parties that collect interest-based information on the Services do not participate in the industry-developed opt-out website, in which case the best way to avoid third-party tracking of your online behaviors may be through your browser settings and deletion of cookies.
How We Use Personal Information Collected Through The Services
Generally, we use the Personal Information we collect through the Services:
to provide the information, products and services you request;
for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
to provide you with effective customer service;
to provide you with a personalized experience when you use the Services;
to contact you with special offers (including sweepstakes) and other information we believe will be of interest to you (in accordance with applicable law and any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
to contact you with information and notices related to your use of the Services;
to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
to better understand your needs and interests;
to improve the content, functionality and usability of the Services;
to improve our products and services;
to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; and
for any other purpose identified in an applicable privacy notice, click-through agreement or other agreement between you and us.
Please see below for information about the choices you have about the ways we use your Personal Information.
Links to Other Websites
The Services may provide links to other websites operated by third parties. We expect our partners, providers of content and services, and advertisers to be transparent about their data protection practices. Be aware, however, that we have no control over third-party websites. This Policy does not apply to Personal Information collected on any third-party website. When you access third-party websites through a link on the Services, please take a few minutes to review the privacy policy posted on that website.
User Generated Content
The User Generated Content you submit on or through the Services is available to others who visit the Services. In addition, we may use User Generated Content you submit on or through the Services in advertising campaigns and other promotions. We may or may not use your name in connection with such use, and we may or may not seek your consent before using the content for such purposes.
Therefore, you should have no expectation of privacy with respect to User Generated Content you submit on or through the Services. You should not submit any content you do not wish to make available to the general public, and you must take special care to make sure your submissions comply with our Terms of Use. In particular, your submissions must not violate the privacy or other rights of others.
Use of Aggregated Information
We may use information gathered through the Services to create a compiled, aggregate view of the Services’ audiences and their visitors’ usage patterns. We use aggregated information to operate our services and to better understand our audience as we develop new products and services. We may also share aggregated information with our third-party service providers as well as with potential investors, advertisers, and subscribers so they can better understand and/or market to our audience. For example, we might share that a certain percentage of our users are female or within a certain age range or live within a cluster of zip codes. Aggregate information is not personally identifiable.
Use of Survey Information
From time to time, we may post a survey on the Services or, if we have your contact information and your consent, we may send you a questionnaire or survey. We compile statistical information from the responses to our surveys. These statistics are not personally identifiable. These statistics help us understand the needs and preferences of the groups we serve and improve the content and functionality of the Services.
Your Choices
In General.  We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your Personal Information. We will include an “opt out” link in each promotional email we send you, so that you can inform us that you do not wish to receive such communications from us in the future.
Previously Expressed Preferences. You may change previously expressed preferences regarding how we use your Personal Information (including opting-out of marketing communications) through your account.
Do Not Track Mechanisms.  Because of the changing state of technology and indecision within the industry regarding the meaning of DNT signals, we currently do not make any guarantee that we will honor DNT signals.
How to Access, Update or Correct Your Personal Information
You can access, update or correct Personal Information related to your ‘Profile’ on the Services by visiting your profile settings. If you are unclear as to how to access, update or correct your Personal Information, please contact us at marketing@montmush.com. We will respond to you within a reasonable time and, in any case, within the time limits established by applicable law. We may ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, we will provide access and correct or delete any inaccurate information you discover. In some cases, however, we may limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so or if we are unable to verify your identify.
Steps We Take to Safeguard your Personal Information
We maintain reasonable administrative, physical and technological measures to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information you submit on or through the Services. For example, when collecting credit card information for online purchases, we offer secured-service transactions through a third-party payment processor. Unfortunately, no website, server or database is completely secure or “hacker proof.” We therefore cannot guarantee that your Personal Information will not be disclosed, misused or lost by accident or by the unauthorized acts of others.  Further, we cannot control dissemination of Personal Information contained in User Generated Content you post on or through our Services, and you should have no expectation of privacy in such information.
How We Share Your Personal Information With Others
Third–Party Service Providers. Monterey Mushrooms shares Personal Information collected through the Services with third-party service providers who act for or on behalf of Monterey Mushrooms. For example, we may use third-party vendors to design, operate, and/or host the Services, to conduct sweepstakes, and to help us with our promotional efforts. These third parties may need information about you to perform their functions.
With Other Users of the Services. The User Generated Content you submit on or through the Services is available to others who visit the Services. Any Personal Information contained in User Generated Content you submit can be read, collected, or used by others, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. In addition, we may use User Generated Content you submit on or through the Services in connection with our news gathering and reporting activities or for advertising campaigns and other promotions. We may or may not use your name in connection with such use, and we may or may not seek your consent before using the content for such purposes. Therefore, you should have no expectation of privacy with respect to User Generated Content you submit on or through the Services. You should not submit any content you do not wish to make available to the general public, and you must take special care to make sure your submissions comply with our Terms of Use. In particular, your submissions must not violate the privacy or other rights of others.
With Other Carefully Selected Business Partners. From time to time, we may share your Personal Information with selected third parties (other than our service providers) for their own marketing purposes. For example, we partner with third parties to sponsor contests or other promotions, and we may share with these third parties the Personal Information you submit to us to participate in the contest or take advantage of the promotion. Before doing so, however, we may offer you the opportunity to “opt out” or “opt in” as required by applicable law. In some cases, you will not be able to participate in a contest or take advantage of a promotion unless you consent to disclosure to our business partner of the Personal Information you submit in connection with the contest or promotion.
With Our Licensors, Service Providers and any of our Affiliates.  We may share the information collected through the Services with any of our affiliates, service providers and licensors (collectively “Other Parties”). Our Other Parties may use the information in all the ways listed in this Policy, provided that such use relates to services authorized by Monterey Mushrooms.
Business Negotiations. We may contemplate, for strategic or other reasons, selling, buying, merging, or otherwise reorganizing one or more of our businesses. In negotiating with a third-party about entering into such an arrangement, we may need to disclose your Personal Information. In such cases, we will take reasonable measures to protect the Personal Information we disclose, for example, by requiring a prospective purchaser to sign a non-disclosure agreement limiting the use and protecting the confidentiality of the Personal Information.
Business Transfers. We may transfer the Personal Information you submit on or through the Services to any organization that acquires or merges with us.
Compliance with Laws and Protection of Our Rights and the Rights of Others. We may disclose your Personal Information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose your Personal Information to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to protect the security of the Services; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.
With Third-Party Social Media Platforms. We may provide functionality on the Services that allows you to automatically post information to a third-party social media platform (such as Facebook, Twitter, or Pinterest). If you choose to take advantage of this functionality, people with access to your profile on the third-party platform will be able to see your post. Thus, you should have no expectation of privacy in those actions. Further, if you choose to link your profile on the Services with an account on a third-party social media platform, we may share the information in your profile with that third-party platform. We may also use third-party social media platforms to offer you interest-based ads. To offer such ads, we may convert your email address into a unique value which can be matched by our partner company with a user on their platform. Although we do not provide any personal information to these platform vendors, they may gain insights about individuals who respond to the ads we serve.
In Aggregate or De-Identified Form. We may use information collected through the Services to create a compiled, aggregate view of usage patterns. We may share aggregate information with third parties, so we and they can better understand our user base. We may also share with third parties information about how particular individuals use the Services, but only on a de-identified basis (“Individualized Data”). Individualized Data is not personally identifiable, but it does reflect the usage patterns of a particular website user, as opposed to website users collectively. We may provide basic demographic information (gender and age) in conjunction with providing Individualized Data. Third parties typically use this information for analytical purposes and to market their own products and services.
As Described in a Privacy Notice. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as described in any privacy notice posted on a page of the Services where you provide that information. By providing your Personal Information on that page you will be consenting to the disclosure of your Personal Information as described in that privacy notice.
As Described in a Click–Through Agreement. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as described in any click–through agreement to which you have agreed.
Children Under the Age of Thirteen
The Services is not intended for children or minors under the age of thirteen years without the permission of a parent or guardian. If you believe that a child has submitted Personal Information on or through the Services without the consent and supervision of a parent or guardian, please contact us using the information provided below so that we can take appropriate action.
Bruce Knobeloch
260 Westgate Drive, Watsonville, CA 95076
This Policy May Change
This Policy describes Monterey Mushrooms’ current policies and practices with regard to the Personal Information we collect through the Services.
We are continually improving and adding to the features and functionality of the Services and the services we offer through the Services. As a result of these changes (or changes in the law), we may need to update or revise this Policy. Accordingly, we reserve the right to update or modify this Policy at any time, without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy behind the link marked “Privacy Policy” in the universal footer of the websites governed by this Policy and by making it available through the mobile and tablet applications governed by this Policy. Your continued use of the Services after we have posted the revised Policy constitutes your agreement to be bound by the revised Policy and your agreement that any information we previously collected from you may be used as described in the revised Policy.
Whenever this Policy is changed, we will update the “effective date” at the top of this page. If you have not used the Services recently, be sure you check the effective date to see if this Policy has been revised since your last visit.
You may access the current version of this Policy at any time by clicking the link marked “Privacy Policy” in the universal footer of our website.
Definitions
The term “Content” refers to all of the software and code comprising or used to operate the Services, and all of the text, photographs, images, illustrations, graphics, sound recordings, video and audio-video clips, and other materials available on the Services, including User Generated Content.
The term “User Generated Content” refers to all of the text, photographs, images, illustrations, graphics, sounds, video, audio-video clips, and other content you post on or through the Services using the social networking tools we make available to registered members of the Services. One way that User Generated Content differs from other information you provide to us is that, once submitted, User Generated Content is made available instantaneously to others who visit the Services. Examples of User Generated Content include comments and photos posted to discussion boards.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us using the information provided below:
Monterey Mushrooms, Inc. 260 Westgate Drive Watsonville, CA 95076
Toll-free: (800) 333-Mush (6874) Fax: (831) 763-2300
